LOUIS ANTOINE

ADDRESS:

42 Nicholls Avenue, Uxbridge, Middlesex, UB8 3JL

PHONE:

+44 (0)748 428 1383

EMAIL:

louisantoine466@gmail.com

PERSONAL STATEMENT

An experienced IT Analyst, with a demonstrated history of working in the Technology & Services industry, supporting businesses for their bespoke needs. I am now looking to sustain longevity in a role, where training and support can be provided to increase my technical abilities. I have held a Full UK Driving License for 4 years.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Harlington Sports Centre, April 2014 - March 2017 | Recreational Assistant

At Harlington Sports Centre I was employed as a Recreational Assistant. Whilst working in a sports centre environment, I gained experience in teamwork, public relations, health and safety awareness, event experience and gained team leadership qualities. I was able to get a good understanding of the qualities needed to provide great customer service to a vast number of people.

Transputec, September 2015 - October 2016 | Senior Configurations Engineer

At Transputec, I was employed as a Senior Configurations Engineer. During my time at Transputec, I have been a supervisor to an Intern. Whilst at Transputec, I developed an understanding of basic IT hardware. I have become familiar with the various ticketing programs, including how to log issues, closing completed job and escalating matters. I have captured and deployed a number of operating images; I have done this using a variety of imaging software. This includes Clonezilla, Symantec Ghost, Acronis and SCCM. I have worked within a number of Windows operating systems, including, Windows, 7, 8, 8.1 and 10. I have also worked on various client sites supporting users from a helpdesk; BAM Construction and The London Metal Exchange.

Virtual Tech Solutions, October 2016 - February 2018 | Technical Analyst

In October 2016, I was hired by a Technical Consultancy in Ickenham to provide technical support as a technical analyst. Responsibilities included account lockouts, password resets, creating mailboxes and distribution groups, to more advanced issues including network troubleshooting, reservations in DHCP, mail filtration and more. Working for Virtual Tech allowed me to gather an excellent understanding of working within SLAS but also working to the expectation of customers.

AzteQ Solutions, February 2018 - August 2018 | ICT Field Engineer

Providing IT support for Schools - In this role, I managed two state Schools, and one Trust split into four academies. The role was field based. This role has helped me to understand the key IT aspects that affect the production environment. It also helped me to understand some of the basic concepts behind GDPR.

Transputec, September 2018 - November 2018 | 2nd Line IT Engineer

A temporary role, supporting internal and external clients at 2nd Line level.

Argos Multidrop Courier, December 2018 - January 2019 | Courier

While searching for the right IT job, I worked temporarily at an agency delivering parcels for Argos.

Davies Turner, February 2019 - April 2019 | IT Administrator

I was providing support to a large RDSH Farm environment, supporting over 1000 users across multiple sites, remotely and face to face. Technologies included Vsphere Client, RDS Broker, NAS storage, load balancing, event sentry, event viewer, update packages, uni print, mail marshall, force point, task scheduling, group policy, backup exec, quantum tape drives and more.

EDUCATION

The Douay Martyrs School, September 2008 - June 2013 GCSE				
Religious Studies - A	Philosophy and Ethics - A	History -	A	Food Technology - B
Core Science - B	ICT Double Award - A / B	English L	anguage - C	English Literature - C
Maths - C	Additional Science - C			

The Douay Martyrs School, September 2013 - May 2014		AS Level	
Applied Business Studies - D	Applied I	T Double Award B / C	

The Douay Martyrs School, September 2014 - June	A2 Level	
Applied Business Studies - E	Applied I	T Double Award C / D

ADDITIONAL QUALIFICATIONS

CompTIA A+ Certified	Level 3 Diploma in ICT Professional Competence		
Advanced Level Apprenticeships in IT, Software,	Level 3 Certificate in ICT Systems and Principles		
Web & Telecoms Professionals			

TECHNICAL SKILLS

SIMS - Deployment	Back-Ups - Checks, Fixes,	Windows 7,8, 8.1 and	Windows Server 2008
	Onsite/Offsite	10	R2, 2012 R2, 2016
Basic Network	Active Directory / Group	Exchange 2007, 2010,	Office 365
Troubleshooting	Policy	2013	
Imagining - Clonezilla,	Laptop Repairs &	Network Printers	DNS
Acronis & WDS	Upgrades		
DHCP	Server Monitoring	Hyper-V	VMWare

INTERESTS

I have a passionate interest in technology; I like to keep myself involved within various tech websites. I partake in various IT training programs, for instance, CBT Nuggets - delving into new technologies and touching base on the old stuff too. I have configured a small home network on an instance of Server 2016, providing DNS and DHCP. I have an interest in sport, following Arsenal FC and often attend matches. I like to keep active by going to the gym and playing football.

REFERENCES

References available on request